icemachinesplus.com 2016-04-01

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

## Information We Collect

The information we gather from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience.

Here are the types of information we gather:

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.  We DO NOT have access to, nor do we store, your credit card information.  You can choose not to provide certain information while browsing our Web site, but this can limit your access to many of our features.  We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your inquiries and questions, customizing future shopping for you when you return to the Web site, improving our online store, and communicating with you.

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Web site. 

## Cookies

Our Web site uses “cookies” to improve our customer’s shopping experience. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable our Web site to relate your use of the site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. 

## Sharing Customer Information

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and it helps us better serve you.

We do not share or sell any customer information.

We do work in conjunction with other companies and individuals to fulfill your order and ship it to you.  These other companies only have access to address information needed to perform their functions, and do not use it for other purposes.

We will release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

## Information Security

We take the security of our customers very seriously.  We will always put the protection of your personal information and credit card data first.  We guarantee that your online purchase will be 100% secure.  Our website and ecommerce use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which is an encryption technology that encodes and protects your information.

We only can access the last four digits of your credit card numbers and will access this only when confirming an order.  Our Web site automatically transmits the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing through a secure, electronic connection.
